The snow glows white on the mountain tonight
皑皑白雪覆盖今夜的山
Not a footprint to be seen
埋藏身后我的足迹
A kingdom of isolation and it looks like I'm the Queen
在这孤独白色国度，我就像是那冰雪的女王
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
狂风呼号，内心亦涌动不能平息
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
再无法藏匿，上天知道我多么努力
Don't let them in, don't let them see
别让别人知道，别让别人看到
Be the good girl
做个好姑娘
You always had to be
你必须一直都是
Conceal, don't feel
要隐藏，不要动真情
Don't let them know
不要让别人知道
Well, now they know
好吧，现在他们知道了
Let it go
随他吧
Can't hold it back anymore
反正再也无法隐瞒
Let it go
不管他
不害怕
Turn away and slam the door
转过身 关上门
I don't care
别人的话
What they're going to say
何必在乎它
Let the storm rage on
就让狂风怒号
The cold never bothered me anyway
严寒再也无法干扰我
It's funny how some distance
可笑的是
Makes everything seem small
距离使一切变得渺小
And the fears that once controlled me
曾经控制我的恐惧
Can't get to me at all
再也无法困扰我
It's time to see what I can do
是时候展现真正的我了
To test the limits and break through
突破我的极限
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
没有对错，没有规则再束缚我
I'm free
我自由了
Let it go
随心而行
I am one with the wind and sky
[我驾驭着狂风和天空
Let it go
随心而行
You'll never see me cry
你将永远看不到我哭
Here I stand
我站在这里
And here I stay
我将待在这里
Let the storm rage on
任那狂风怒号
My power flurries through the air into the ground
我的魔力从天而降
My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around
我的灵魂随着四周的冰片盘旋而上
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
思想化为结晶 如一阵冰风
I'm never going back
我不会再回头
The past is in the past
过去已经成为往事
Let it go
让它过去吧
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
我将像旭日从地上升起
Let it go
随心而行
That perfect girl is gone
那个完美的女孩已经不在了
Here I stand in the light of day
我就站在日光之下
Let the storm rage on
让风暴怒吼吧
The cold never bothered me anyway
严寒无法再侵扰我